https://www.oxfordhomesinc.com/wpautoterms/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentYou Are HerePrivacy Policy
Oxford Housing Inc
September 3, 2019
no Comments Last updated: September 3, 2019Oxford Housing Inc (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the Oxford Housing Inc website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://www.oxfordhomesinc.comInformation Collection And UseWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:NameEmail addressTelephone numberAddressLog DataWe collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.Google AdSense & DoubleClick CookieGoogle, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.Compliance With LawsWe will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.Post navigationTerms and ConditionsRecent PostsOutdoor Lighting & Direct Pendant Lighting Ideas for Your HomeNovember 1, 2020Getting the right light fixtures and bulbs for each room of your home can be a challenge, but if you plan it out correctly, they can help you enjoy the …Read More »Expert’s Quick Guide To Buying Your Perfect Runescape Gold JewelryOctober 7, 2020The world has been in love with gold ever since it was discovered. It is called a precious metal because it has a high economic value and is relatively scarce …Read More »Get a Tennis court resurfacing For Your HomeJuly 7, 2020Visualize this; a class with a racket for everyone, more than enough tennis balls,Tennis court resurfacing a rolled up blue mat that stands about 3 ½ feet tall, Colored tape, …Read More »Top 3 reasons to keep your roof cleanMay 26, 2020Cleaning your roof may seem like a waste of time, but it certainly is beneficial. Most people, when it comes to cleaning their properties, exterior surfaces, will attend to the …Read More »The Best Oil Water Separator DesignDecember 26, 2019The Best Oil Water Separator Design The Best Oil Water Separator Design From your authentic oil normal water separator layout initially mounted from the API (American citizen Oil Institute) in …Read More »
Terms and Conditions - Privacy Policy
